You can't be a land man
and the president.
- Why not?
- You should be in fort worth.
- for one.
- Well. who's gonna do what I do here?
I'm sorry. I don't remember
the last time I saw people just be happy.
If we're gonna do this. then let's do it.
Both feet. I don't need a roommate.
You want to get married?
My god.
- How about that drink?
- Please.
- Hi.
- Morning.
We're happy to partner.
We don't need partners.
That's not what your boss says.
She told me everything.
I am the fucking solution.
so I'll be here waiting.
You killed a man in front of me.
I know what your money
is. and I can't have it
anywhere near us.
You don't know where
his money comes from.
- I know.
- You think you do. but. no.
you don't and neither do I. I will not lose
the company my husband started
eight weeks after taking it over.
You have our attorneys
meet with his and paper it.
Well. it's that time of year.
The permian basin international
oil show has come to town.
What does that mean for the basin?
Traffic.
Gonna be some traffic.
Yeah. you can forget about
making that dinner reservation.
Best you. eat at home this week.
Well. pretty good week to be a stripper.
Hey. you can't say that.
Exotic dancer.
Very exotic. So I've heard.
Yeah. I've just heard rumors.
They are all true.
Here's a new one from
the turnpike troubadours.
Please. for god's sake. shut the fuck up
and play the song.
I know. you-you like 'em.
Quit talking about it.
That shit's gonna kill you. you know.
Yeah. well. that's a pretty fair trade
for all the joy it's given me.
You're up early.
Up the same time I'm always up.
Well. when I retire.
my goal is to never see
another fucking sunrise again.
How come you're seeing it today?
I got to drive to fort worth.
Want some company?
Pop. all I do is roll calls for three hours.
putting fires out.
Then I have a meeting.
and then I do three hours
of the same shit on the way back.
I'll keep my mouth shut.
I ain't looking for company.
You shouldn't litter.
Well. it's my fucking pool.
If it's somebody else's
pool. then it'd be littering.
Fine. then you shouldn't
be such a fucking slob.
And you don't look like
you ought to be giving out advice.
Goddamn it.
I'll be out front if you want to go with me.
All right.
You better get ready.
I'm ready now.
Morning. baby.
Morning. sweetheart.
Honey?
C-Could you please
put all your clothes on
before you come downstairs?
It bothers you to see my body?
No. hell no. it don't bother me. I...
But there's other
people around here. shit.
Does this bother you. Thomas?
It ain't bothering me.
Morning. everybody.
- Hey. Dale.
- Hey.
Does this outfit bother you?
This feels like a trick question.
- Morning.
- I'm gonna get
- my coffee on the road.
- Hi.
- Hey. daddy.
- You know what? I give up.
I love you both. and there's
nothing I can do about that.
I fucking surrender.
I don't know.
Will you be home for supper?
Well. it depends on what the theme is.
Well. since we already did seafood.
I mean. I'm thinking Mexican.
- Ooh. Yeah.
- Fun?
Can't imagine all the
ways that will be offensive.
In no way will it be offensive. Neil.
It will be festive and fun.
She does this on purpose.
You know that. right?
I have detected the pattern.
- Yeah. I know.
- If you say
something nice. I will
use your real name.
But if you act like a
Neil. I will call you Neil.
All right. I'm out.
- I love you. girls. Love you.
- Love you. baby.
Love you. Thomas.
Have a great day.
- How are you doing. bud? Dale.
- Doing good.
Dale. good to meet you.
Nice to meet you. man.
Hey. you familiar with one of these?
Loads the pipe. trips
it. and it drops it down.
Okay. now. it used to be
old boys throwing chain.
All right? Now they're not even gonna be
working the tongue no more?
That's right. Four-man
crew becomes one.
Is that a good thing?
- Crew cost drop by 75%.
- Right.
Insurance liabilities
drop by a factor of four.
and on top of that.
you reduce your trucking
fleet. reduce your housing.
- reduce any sort of...
- yeah. I got it.
- I got it. I got it.
- Look. I'll tell you what.
We got a working model
outside. if you want to go see.
I'm just window-shopping. buddy.
- Can I grab that hot sauce?
- Yeah. of course.
- Awesome.
- Hey. she got a bite.
- Be careful. all right?
- Thanks. dude. Good luck to you.
- Hey. it's worth checking out.
- All right.
- It's the wave of the future.
- I'm sure it is.
Would you look at all this shit here?
It's fucking wild. bro.
Hey. boss.
Boss. they got planes for sale
over there across the street.
- What kind of planes?
- Like big ones. like jets.
How the hell they get
jets across the street?
Well. they landed them
here in the middle of the night.
I guess. I-I don't know.
What?
Ain't no way they land
a jet in a parking lot. br.
You know. sometimes
you just a... a dizzy
motherfucker. You know that?
I've seen stranger things in this town.
Okay. you guys tell me
how they got 'em here.
because they damn
sure didn't drive them.
- Hey.
- What y'all selling over here?
Nothing.
Something being sold.
- Y'all want some caps?
- Hell yeah.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Want a picture with the car?
You in the picture?
I am if you want me to be.
Girl. that's the only reason to take it.
- Hold my beer?
- Sure.
All right. you guys ready?
Say "dipshit."
- Thank you. guys.
- Here you go.
Thank you.
How about you?
Why? So my wife
can find it on Instagram
with you and... All that going on?
Not a chance. ma'am.
Thank you. though.
- Bye.
King. would you just
look at all this shit. man?
You said that already.
Well. I'm saying it again.
Look at all this money. man.
I mean. this is just what they
can make off oil companies.
Hey. boss.
What the hell is that?
That's the future.
Without us.
That's what it is.
Starting to crawl.
He's trying to.
Yep. there he goes.
Next thing. he'll be walking
and you'll be running.
and the race is on.
How's work?
Noisy.
Serving drinks to a bunch of people
who have no business drinking.
What did you do with
the insurance money?
That's Miguel's money.
It's your money. too.
No.
It's Miguel's.
He lost a father for it.
He's not the only one who lost.
So...
what's with this skinny boy?
Cooper.
Yes.
He's in corpus.
For work?
No. not work.
What. then?
I want you to hear this from me first.
Not rumors. not...
I never expected I'd
ever fall in love again.
Are you sure it's love
and not something else?
No. I know it's love because skinny.
stray dog-looking white
men are not my type.
I know it's love because...
because this thing tells me every day
that he's wrong.
But my heart...
Only listen to that one.
He's going to ask me to marry him.
You think?
I know.
I told him to.
But I want you to be...
And I know it's not my place to say that.
But I hope and pray...
I'm not trying to replace elvio.
This is the last thing I ever expected.
You deserve to be happy.
If he gives you that. then good.
Elvio is gone. You can love a memory.
but he can't love you back.
You're still a young woman
with passion in her heart.
You need to be loved back.
But I want to look in this boy's eyes
and see for myself.
You send him over when he's back.
¿Sí?
Amorcito. Ay. ¿por qué estás llorando?
Well. they sure
have pincushioned the
world with them frack Wells.
Not them. pop. You.
How many of those fucking
things did you stick in the dirt?
I never drilled in the basin.
I ain't never drilled a frack well in my life.
In my day wildcatters understood terrain.
They'd just look at the land
and know there was oil under it.
Please tell me I don't have to listen
to this shit for three fucking hours.
What happened to just looking
out the window and being quiet?
What happened to the
50 fucking business calls
you had to take?
They're coming. believe me.
Well. when they show up. I'll shut up.
Well. I'll be damned
if there ain't one now.
See what I'm saying?
What's the verdict?
Well. I'm halfway there. I guess.
Son. you ain't halfway to the starting line.
I need to see you.
I'm headed to fort worth.
All right. I'll meet you there.
It can't wait?
I need something for the leases.
Well. what about the
$42 million dollars of debt
that I just paid off?
Dad. they're worth ten times that each.
Well. you'd have more if you'd
have secured a legitimate loan
and formed a legitimate company
and paid your fucking bills.
So I-I don't get anything?
Well. you're getting your
first check in three weeks.
I need a ring.
- Goddamn it.
- A wedding ring.
And you need that today?
- Yes.
- It can't wait two or three months?
Or at least till I get
back to fucking midland?
No. it can't wait.
He's a patient child. isn't he?
Wonder where he got that from.
How much do you need?
I don't know.
How much do they cost?
Beats the shit out of me. I don't know.
Call your mother. She knows all that shit.
- All right. I'll call you back.
- Hey. hey.
Hang on. Cooper. Don't call your mother.
Son of a bitch.
Goddamn. Had to
open my fucking mouth.
It's gonna cost me $100.000 right there.
Do you have $100.000?
Not having it don't stop my wife
from spending it. believe me.
My ex-wife. Sometimes I
forget we're not married.
I'd say you're pretty fucking married. son.
Yeah.
It's hot in here today.
I tipped that cute boy
at the front desk $100
to crank the heat.
I never understood
ac blasting at the gym.
I'm not here to be comfortable.
I'm here to work.
- You know?
- Yeah.
I'm at the gym with your sister.
What are you up to. baby?
Hey. how much do
engagement rings cost?
Why?
Cooper. are you getting married?
I don't know. I'm-I'm gonna ask.
Cooper. that's so exciting.
Your brother's getting married.
Well. make sure the
girl doesn't have a dick.
- Ainsley.
- Well...
No woman could fall in love with him.
Not one that can see or smell. Or hear.
- She has a baby.
- You can buy those
in the parking lot at Walmart.
Hey. Cooper. I'm just checking.
She's a 100% girl. right?
Mom. you've got to quit spending
so much time with Ainsley.
How much are rings?
I mean. you know. I think
they start around $25.000
- for a sorry little...
- whoa.
On zales' website.
they say it's. like. half...
good god. son.
Stay in your little Lane. baby.
No shopping for
diamonds on the Internet.
Go to bachendorf's. or
you can call sue gragg.
Those are your only two options.
Have you talked to
your daddy about this?
Well. he told me to call you.
You know what?
You come by the house.
I'm gonna give you my engagement ring.
Yours?
That way it stays in the family.
and you don't have to start
out your marriage in debt
like your daddy.
Well. can I come pick it up later?
Come by whenever you
want. my little angel face.
All right. thank you. mom. Love you.
I love you. my little squishy bug.
All right. bye.
I could smell him through the phone.
Honey. those are called pheromones.
Your brother's pheromones
are supposed to repulse you.
That's how evolution prevents incest
and six-toed little feet.
Never thought about it like that.
It's true.
So god wants me to hate him.
Hate's a strong word. Ainsley.
Okay? But he sure don't want
you going to prom with him.
Ew.
I got to call your daddy.
Well. hey. babe.
Our baby's getting married?
Yeah. it looks like it's
going in that direction.
Hey. did he talk to you about a ring?
I got him all squared away.
- Yeah. and how'd you do that?
- I gave him mine.
You mean that big old fucking
ugly-ass thing from Victor?
Are you nuts? Good god. no.
That's a 22-carat canary diamond.
I'm giving him the one you got me
since it's tainted with
the stench of failure.
Baby. you got to get me a new one.
And there's no sense in
Cooper spending all that money.
And it gives me something to do.
I'm gonna go ring shopping. baby.
- I need the jet.
- Ooh.
You don't need the fucking jet
to go jewelry shopping. honey.
There's plenty of diamonds in midland.
Honey. look at me.
Diamonds are in Dallas.
Plus. this little one needs
to go school shopping.
I need clothes.
So badly.
Shit. All right. well. the jet's
dead-legging back to
fort worth this afternoon.
- Wait.
- Thanks. daddy.
You're going to fort worth?
Yeah.
Well. let's make a weekend of it.
Don't leave me here.
Well. honey. if it was a weekend.
that'd be one thing. but it ain't.
Baby. Friday is when the weekend starts.
I don't want to hear one more thing.
I'll plan everything. I'm
gonna meet you at cattlemen's.
We're gonna have so
much fun. I love you.
- Mwah. Whoo!
- Thank you.
H-Hang on a...
Well. pop...
I was wrong.
Hundred grand ain't gonna scratch
the surface on this shit.
You know those little
monkeys they put on the back
of border collies at the rodeos?
Yeah.
Border collie runs all over the place.
monkey's just trying to hang on.
No control over where it's going.
No way to get off without fucking dying.
Crowd laughing at him as he whips by.
That's you.
Fuck you.
You're the monkey on a runaway dog.
Shit.
Typically. the rig would
be tugged out of port
down the mouth of the
Mississippi into open water.
And this is the rig location here?
In the Gulf of Mexico?
America.
That is currently its legal name.
The Gulf.
Let's just call it the Gulf.
That's the location of
the rig's future home.
Correct. Replacing the rig
we lost to Francine in 2024.
I'm assuming Francine is a hurricane.
Correct. And since we
previously had a well there.
we know the location of that well.
We can bypass most of the due diligence
prior to sending the rig to sea.
Once it's in the region. we can set it
and drill as close as
possible to the previous well.
Why not just reconnect
it to the existing well?
Integrity of the wellhead
was compromised.
There's no way to repair it. It's too deep.
What's the timeline to drill another well?
End of the year.
And how much can it produce?
Old well produced 200
million cubic feet a day.
Help me understand
that in dollar figures.
Gross revenue's over a billion a year.
Depending on almost countless factors.
one would hope for an roi of 20%.
At that volume.
with a price increase
from today's price of $3.47
to a peak of $15.78 in 2005.
you can 5x that percentage.
Do we have an offshore geologist
who can oversee this project?
Possibly. We have one
who worked offshore for BP.
- What's his name?
- Newsom.
- I should meet him.
- What for?
There is an offshore well
none of you knew about
that generated $150
million in net revenue a year.
And rather than spend
an insurance payout
to continue that revenue stream.
monty chose to take that
money and spend it on a field
of work over rigs with
no guarantee of a return.
I don't have time to
explain the game to you.
My god. I don't care. and that is why
I want to meet with someone who can.
Not an attorney and not the fix-it man
who found himself
president of an oil company.
A scientist.
I'd like to meet with this newsom.
I assume he has some
sort of field office or...
I'll send you a pin.
5 P.M.
"Please"?
If you're gonna treat me
like a fucking secretary.
you could have the common
decency to be polite about it.
If you would be so kind
as to inform Mr. Newsom
I will meet him at five. it
would be greatly appreciated.
- I will let him know.
- And I will be reporting
your use of profanity to hr.
I am the head of hr. so
consider your complaint filed.
Nothing about this is how
a company should be run.
Says the 29-year-old
who's never run a company.
All right.
Damn. this town has changed.
Well. this damn brick
road hasn't changed.
Feels like it's gonna
rattle my fucking teeth out.
I remember they
drove cattle up this road.
They still drive cattle up this road. pop.
Only difference is.
now it's for the tourists.
not for the packers.
This ain't gonna take long.
You mind staying in the truck?
Hell yes. I mind staying in the truck.
I'm 80. not eight.
Can't leave your kids in
the truck anymore. pop.
Well. you're sure as
hell not gonna leave me
sitting in the truck.
All right. fine.
Wow. that looks dangerous.
It is dangerous.
But there's a beauty to it.
It's like a violent ballet.
I'm surprised you
haven't seen this before.
Well. you know. there's...
There's two fort worths.
and I don't live in this one.
Shit.
Pop. you just hang around
here for a minute. all right?
- If you get hungry. -here's some money...
- I got money.
Really?
Well. why are you living in
the spare room in my house
- if you got money?
- I got money for a hot dog.
I ain't got enough for a fucking house.
All right. well. just stay here.
You in the market for one?
Not for a long time.
Still like looking at 'em. though.
Yeah. they ain't changed much.
Everything else sure has.
Yeah.
This one's yours?
Well. it's-it's kit's horse.
- This is kit's horse.
- Well...
- Cami.
- Hey. kit. How are you?
Good. How are y'all?
Good.
It's kit's horse. but I
manage the syndicate.
So. what's this horse's name?
His name is noche.
But his full name is
noche oscura del Alma.
which means "the dark night of the soul."
Well. that is quite a
unique name for a horse.
It's from a poem by
St. John of the cross.
It means different
things to different people.
but for me it's about...
About finding comfort
in. in a time of crisis.
You're in a time of crisis. I believe.
Maybe you should read it.
I will.
Mucho. noche.
Hey. I didn't know you
were a horseman. Tommy.
No. I like motorcycles.
They're faster and you don't
have to feed 'em.
You're too practical. Tommy.
But there's no art in riding a motorcycle.
This is art.
Yeah. maybe the art
of money laundering.
If I wanted to launder
money. I'd invest in a franchise
of tanning salons and be done with it.
How you doing. cami? I
didn't know you were coming.
Well. why wouldn't I?
I mean. it's my company.
Nash. Peters.
Your roughneck for magnolia.
Before the crash.
Yes. sir.
How you been?
Well. still breathing.
You?
How do I look like I've been?
At least you ain't wearing
one of these things.
That's 'cause I'm too
crippled to commit a crime.
You were never no outlaw.
You ain't looking much
outlaw these days either.
Well. this is for bouncing checks.
How outlaw is that?
Not very.
Still got that pretty wife?
Pretty wife died.
Sorry to hear it.
Heart died a while ago.
Just took her body 40 years to catch up.
You into the horses?
Nash?
I doubt we talked this much
when we worked together.
I don't see any point in doing it now.
You were always a dick.
Yeah. maybe so. but I ain't
the one picking up trash.
Where's the geologist?
He's in his office.
Excuse me. ma'am. you can't park here.
Fuck.
Wasn't gonna be the
first thing I mentioned.
but I'm glad it's out in the open.
Nate said you needed a crash course
in getting drilled offshore.
- Drilling a well offshore.
- Yes.
- Well. I'm your man.
- Can the double entendres
cease. please?
That's not what I meant.
We have a hard deadline
of 45 days to launch a rig.
and I do not understand
the hurdles we will face.
Well. there will be plenty.
and I can explain them to you.
Want to come in?
No. I do not.
Want to sit on the tailgate of my truck
where you have plenty of witnesses?
- Better.
- All right.
You look beautiful.
You understand that
a romantic relationship
with an m-Tex employee
violates the stipulations of your contract?
It actually states that
a romantic relationship
with a subordinate
violates the agreement.
which means you're the only
one who violated the contract.
you little lawbreaker. you.
God.
Take ten months to set the well.
Once it's on-line. we
go 70-30. 70 my way.
I'll pay you back 20% to service debt.
When the loan's paid. it's 50-50.
but it's a true split.
We split everything.
We split the overhead.
the maintenance. all of it.
You got your numbers backwards.
The fuck I do.
I'm paying the rig expenses
and servicing debt.
and you're making 30%.
60-40 with a 30% promoter off the top.
I can't cash flow the rig.
I'll give you a pick rate.
And no debt service
until your well is on-line...
no. I'm not my son. I don't loan to lose.
60-40. with a 20% promote.
All the 40 goes to the debt service
until the loan is paid off.
then it remains a 60-40.
but the promote goes away.
And we share the expenses
on the same scale. 60-40.
That sounds like a good deal.
It's a forgiving deal.
It shows you the kind of...
partner I can be.
Tommy?
If you agree. I'll have
my attorneys paper it.
- I agree.
- We're not done
- negotiating yet. cami...
- we're done now.
Our attorneys paper it and you red line it.
It's my new goal in life.
Tommy. to have you trust me.
That's a pretty lofty goal.
You can paper it.
You son of a bitch.
Fuck you.
I'll be back.
- Get up. - you son of a bitch.
- Get off me!
Get off me. Don't you run away. old man!
Get up here. you bastard.
Get up here. See what the fuck happens.
- Let me go. boy.
- Don't you run away from me!
Hey. What in the
goddamn hell did you do?
- Come here.
- Say it again
- and see what happens.
- Pop. come here.
Come here. goddamn it.
- Come here.
- Fuck you!
Hey. hey. Hey. guys.
- help me handle this. will you?
- Yep.
- I got it. I got it.
- Hey! Come here.
Come up here and see what happens.
Pop. get your ass over here.
Come here!
Come on. come on.
You go sit in the fucking truck.
One of these days. you'll be in my shoes.
We'll see what happens then.
I tell you what. if I was in your shoes.
I'd be hot-footing it to that fucking truck
and talking me out of
getting into fucking jail.
That's what I'd be doing. Goddamn it.
Hey. guys.
Guy's on a work crew for the county.
- He's not saying anything.
- All right. So. we good here?
Yeah. just get him out
of here. I'll take care of it.
I will.
Fuck.
- Everything all right?
- Yes. ma'am.
Tommy's dad. It's all good.
You okay?
It's always a loaded
question with me. cami.
Well. we're gonna go and
take a look at the stallion.
- Join us. Come on.
- No. I got a horse's ass
of my own to deal with.
Well. we're gonna be celebrating tonight.
- Join us tonight.
- Well. I've got my wife
and my father. and as you can tell.
- he's an outdoor cat. so...
- Tommy.
Not business. just wives and celebration.
Can't wait.
Hey. pop? What in the world?
You should take me back to the home.
This ain't working.
You know. you're lucky you're
not wearing an orange vest
at the next fucking horse show in there.
cleaning up trash cans right beside him.
You think I give a shit?
It's pretty clear you don't give a shit.
I wonder what somebody
would have to say about Angela.
Angela can take care of herself.
Ainsley. then.
Did he know mama?
Is that it?
Did he say something about
mama? Did he call her a whore
or an addict or a thief or something?
'Cause it's true.
I'm glad you don't understand.
Because I barely understand it.
And I lost a child. too.
And she didn't grow inside me.
My body didn't nourish her.
It shattered me. but it
didn't scramble my soul.
It scrambled her soul. son.
And you never got to
meet the most joyous...
loving creature that I've ever seen
on this fucking planet.
You could say I wasted
my life and ruined yours.
and maybe I did.
but for the hope that maybe
she was in there somewhere. son.
Well. pop. I don't think
hers is the only soul
that got scrambled.
Come on. let's go. pop.
Pop. let's go.
Hello. Mrs. Russo.
It's Norris now. sugar.
Should we still bill the Russo account?
We can damn sure try.
Is this all the luggage?
The goal's not to arrive
with luggage. Christian.
The goal is to leave with it.
We're going shopping!
Whoo!
Want a beer?
I don't think you should
be drinking on the job.
It's past five. Job's over.
Well. you have to drive.
I won't leave this site for three days.
not until the well is on-line.
Here.
- I have to drive.
- Not for a while. you don't.
You can be good at your
job and enjoy yourself.
You know that. right?
So... Here we are.
Now. Francine hits this rig
and causes surface damage.
but that's not what shuts it down.
It began pumping water.
which means there
was a blowout in the well.
- A blowout?
- Yeah. offshore.
That is the nightmare.
When horizon blew...
now that's oil. not gas...
it killed a dozen people.
but if a gas well blows...
so. there was a blowout?
Yeah. They shut the well
down. they brought the rig back.
- They did the right thing.
- And now
we're required to drill another one.
with no guarantee we'll find gas?
There's no guarantees.
but a gas field is different than oil.
It's a much more forgiving process.
from an exploration perspective.
You just... You've got
to choose the right spot.
Can you?
Find the right spot?
Are you asking me to?
Yes.
Just so I understand. y-you're asking me
to lead the drill on an offshore rig.
I am asking you to lead the drill
on an offshore rig. yes.
Hey. you can't... That's
assault. you son of a bitch.
- What's so funny?
- It's not funny.
I'm not. I'm not... It's not funny. it's just.
watching your internal
struggle to let yourself feel good.
it's... it's fascinating.
Well. I'm glad you find it so entertaining.
- Yeah. I do.
- We work together.
How many hours a day
do you give your job?
My job?
My job gets all of them.
- Yeah? Right.
- Every hour.
Mine. too.
Where else you gonna meet someone?
There are people everywhere.
There's no people anywhere.
Everyone's gone home.
The town is 15 miles away.
Okay. let's just slow this down.
All right. I'll take you for dinner.
Or I'll make you dinner.
How will you make dinner out here?
How?
I'll take food out of the refrigerator.
Then using a heat source.
maybe the gas burner in my fifth wheel.
maybe some mesquite
wood in the grill. you know.
- I'll make you dinner.
- Don't be an asshole.
I will make you dinner.
- Fine.
- Okay.
- Great.
- Lovely.
Follow me.
Aww. thank you.
Thank you so much.
Let me get those.
Thank you. Christian.
Buying new clothes is so rewarding.
It's like purchasing hope.
That's very well said. baby.
Nothing rids the blues
like a good shopping spree.
You have the blues?
I never have the blues. baby.
My grip is firmly around
the scrotum of life.
and I will never let go.
Hey. babe.
- Where you at?
- I'm sitting at the bar
at cattleman's. waiting on you.
Well. I'm headed your way.
Hope you've got your dancing shoes on.
I do not.
I've got my "sit in the
booth in the corner".
"skulking" shoes on.
Well. you better change your
footwear. Mr. Grumpy pants.
because we're going dancing.
Honey. y-you know
damn well that that's...
I swear. my wife could make mourners
take Tequila shots at a fucking funeral.
Ex-wife.
Ex-wife. thank you.
You ought to remedy that.
And quick.
Before she comes to her senses.
It's on my list.
Move it to the top.
Noted.
What do you got?
Ten years left?
Before climbing on that barstool
is a fucking struggle like it is for me.
before the smoking.
drinking and the rest of it
slows you to a crawl.
Your making-memory days
is about behind you. son.
And trust me.
living off of memories ain't no living at all.
You got to make them...
while you can.
You hear me?
I hear you. pop.
Hola. mi amor.
¿Qué estás haciendo?
Ay. travieso.
What am I gonna do with you?
Yeah?
Come on.
Hi. Hey.
I never noticed the uniforms till now.
They definitely make a statement.
You know. that place can
be pretty rough at night.
Behind the bar is the safest spot.
In front of the bar is a
completely different story.
I spoke to your dad.
I heard.
Hey. do me a favor.
Take Miguel to his abuelita's house.
I can watch him.
No. you're not ready for that.
I am gonna be late.
- I'll be up.
- Real late.
I'll still be up.
Looks like I have two sad dogs
staring at the door
waiting for me to get home.
Well. we'll sit here and suffer together.
I'll make it up to you.
Don't leave my son on the floor.
I got him.
Be careful.
Hey. bud.
You ready?
Come in.
I'm around if you need anything.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Yes. yes.
Here.
No. no. no. Look at me.
Now explain to me why
you should marry my grandson's widow.
Well...
No answer?
I ain't ever...
I've never been in love before.
I didn't even know
what those words meant.
But when I look at her. I
just want to make her happy.
And I'll do whatever I
got to do to achieve that.
Now that I'm with her.
the only thing that
makes me happy is her.
It's kind of got me turned upside down.
I-I've got these butterflies
when I'm with her. and...
I got them when she's gone.
I spend most of my
time sick to my stomach
'cause I'm worried I'm not
doing enough or-or doing it right.
I don't think I'm very good at it.
Part of the problem.
Guess you know what it means after all.
I'm sorry. I'm-I'm just blabbering.
That's what grandmothers are for.
When you need to
blabber. you come to me.
- You hungry?
- N...
Yes. ma'am.
How are you on the grill?
Men must know how
to grill and make salsa.
The rest. we will forgive you.
Come on.
What about Miguel?
Miguel is free to wander.
My house is baby proofed to my knees.
Once he can walk. it's a different story.
Okay.
Don't let her drink too much.
What are you doing?
I'm just taking it all in.
See. that's not gonna work.
See. Friday night is not a spectator sport.
Friday night is
full-contact. and we're about
to have some.
See. your grump of a
son won't dance with me.
I don't see a dance floor.
You see this floor?
Once we start dancing
on this son of a bitch.
dance floor is what it becomes.
I guess I got a dance or two left in me.
All right.
Ainsley!
¡Vamos a bailar!
One. two. one. one...
Your wife has a real gift.
- Well...
- She can get anybody
to shred their inhibitions.
Yeah.
My wife has that. It's very likely
that we're gonna regret
getting them together.
I think the likelihood
of that is guaranteed.
All your worries are
for nothing. my friend.
My two businesses. they never cross.
Except remember that one
time when you drove to Odessa
and killed those drug
dealers in the basement
of a fucking strip club?
I killed because they crossed.
I killed to save you.
There are people in my business
that are starting to feel that
your-your business is better.
Less risk but not less money.
Well. if you ever doubt that. bud.
just walk the streets of acapulco
or spend a couple of days in Dubai.
and you'll know exactly
who has more money.
What's your father's story?
My father's story's over.
Doesn't look like it's over.
It's over.
You know. I get the sense
that she don't trust you.
Me and her husband
started out together.
So. at one point. I had a
version of what she has.
But I didn't hedge it.
Crash of '08 pretty
much cleaned me out.
So I went to work for her husband.
She don't trust me 'cause
she thinks I'm a loser.
And she thinks I'm
gonna lose her fortune.
Well. you're gonna have
to do something about that.
Because when those
sharks smell her doubting you.
they're gonna poison her
with reason to get rid of you.